{
    "subject": "resource/Keith_Varon",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Keith Varon is from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9794298410415649,
            "question": "Is Keith Varon associated with the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9582549333572388,
            "question": "Is Keith Varon American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8634448051452637,
            "question": "Where is Keith Varon from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6796839833259583,
            "question": "What is Keith Varon's country of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272900700569153,
            "question": "Where was Keith Varon raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6248387098312378,
            "question": "To which nation does Keith Varon belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208961606025696,
            "question": "What is Keith Varon's national background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5968961715698242,
            "question": "Keith Varon's citizenship is in which country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5316254496574402,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Keith Varon's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5210729241371155,
            "question": "What country is Keith Varon's birthplace?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Keith Varon is from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8855_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Keith Varon's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8855_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Keith Varon's citizenship is in which country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8855_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Keith Varon's national background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8855_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8855_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Keith Varon is described as an American singer-songwriter and music producer (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8855/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8855/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt). This information supports the triple \"Keith Varon is from the United States\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Keith Varon is an American singer-songwriter, which confirms that he is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}